<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Recent Content on Agigen </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.xml</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 16:56:20 CEST</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>uppsalastudent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/uppsalastudent</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 16:56:20 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/uppsalastudent</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Uppsalastudent&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yogobe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/yogobe</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 16:56:07 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/yogobe</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google I/O - Build with Chrome multiplayer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2014-07-18-google-io-build-with-chrome</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 13:59:36 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2014-07-18-google-io-build-with-chrome</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Build&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billogram</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/billogram</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 13:02:37 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/billogram</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Blog Exchange</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/big-blog-exchange</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 12:56:42 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/big-blog-exchange</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The liberation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/only-the-liberation</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 12:49:40 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/only-the-liberation</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Getaway</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/mini-getaway</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 12:49:26 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/mini-getaway</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beta sj se</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/beta-sj-se</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 15:58:40 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/beta-sj-se</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;tl;dr:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Project for SJ (Swedish railways)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Together with Pond&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Prototype concept for SJ&amp;rsquo;s brand new site&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Revamp, redesign and improve&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    In autumn 2013 a tantalizing prospect was presented to us. Our partner Pond had won the assignment to redo sj.se - Swedish Railways&amp;rsquo; site. It was interesting and exciting for several reasons. It was a huge project; on a magnitude we had seldom worked before. It was technically complex, as our frontend needed to integrate with all the subsystem that was already in use at SJ. But above all, sj.se has for a long, long time been a constant thorn in many people&amp;rsquo;s side; a huge site, difficult to navigate and with a less than satisfactory experience performing its main task: selling tickets.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Regularly using SJ&amp;rsquo;s services ourselves, the prospect of remaking the site into something speedy and easy to use was thrilling. In short, we were so stoked.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What have we done?(!)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Being such a large project it was divided into phases. We started out making a bunch of different prototypes for the start page; testing out different kinds of menus, layouts and use cases. In this project, we really worked more as partners than subcontractors to Pond and they let us in on the creative process, carefully listening to our input on design and UX.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    We all wanted to put the emphasis on what the site was all about: Selling tickets. However, due to technical restrictions we were less than free to do as we saw fit. A lot of the information that we felt made ordering tickets so clumsy and tiresome at the current site, was unfortunately non-negotiable. It had to be there.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    We were a bit stumped, but we focused on what we could control, hoping that the subsystems would catch up and allow for a more flexible booking eventually. We iterated through a lot of different designs, aiming to make the site easy to comprehend and also easy for content providers at SJ to use. We thought a lot about how to draw focus to the right things and how to make the site easy to understand - for everybody. In this was our biggest challenge: There&amp;rsquo;s hardly anyone that hasn&amp;rsquo;t been to SJ&amp;rsquo;s site at some point to order tickets. People of all ages and with very different levels of computer skills.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Eventually we had a prototype that we felt was a good start and that SJ felt was what they wanted as well. It was decided that it would be tested on the general public at an event on Stockholm&amp;rsquo;s Central Station. Random people were invited to test the site, answering questions and being tasked to go about doing certain actions on the prototype. The feedback was collected and brought back to us, to do improvements on the prototype.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    After this, implementatioin at SJ&amp;rsquo;s web department commenced. We were there, helping out for several weeks and the result was beta.sj.se; open to the general public and utilising a new (to us) tool from a company called Usabilla to, again, collect feedback from the users.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Afterwards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    SJ&amp;rsquo;s new site is nowhere near finished, but we&amp;rsquo;re no longer involved. SJ did some serious restructuring of the project plan, and while they still wanted our help, the new plan was nothing like the beginning of the project; we felt much of the passion to change and the openmindedness was lost, and we simply declined.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    We&amp;rsquo;re proud to have been part of the process, and we learned a lot of new things working with such a huge organisation as SJ. We&amp;rsquo;re looking forward to seeing how the end result turns out.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hobbit 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/thehobbit-a-journey</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 12:43:46 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/thehobbit-a-journey</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;tl;dr:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Project for Google and Warner Bros.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Together with North Kingdom&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;An interactive webGL experience set in Middle-Earth&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Explore Middle-Earth and get into the Tolkien-groove by playing mini games set at different locations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    There are quite a few fantasy geeks at our office, and even those not particularly interested will still get their asses to the cinemas when there&amp;rsquo;s a Tolkien film goin up. Imagine our delight at being part of this interactive experience in Middle-Earth, once again partnering up with North Kingdom to create some magic.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What have we done?(!)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    We didn&amp;rsquo;t get to do any of the really cool stuff on this project; our efforts were more in the obscure though challenging nonetheless. The application was to be localized in 43 languages so we decided to create an entire tool solely for translations. It imports and exports json files connecting a key to an element in the HTML. There is also a UI to edit the strings without the fuss of json-files, but as far as we know it was never used by Google (who were in charge of actually providing the translations). It turned out rather well and we have reused it in other applications as well.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    We were also in charge of setting upp the application&amp;rsquo;s hosting on Google App Engine and managing staging versions and deploys.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Afterwards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    It won awards. NK has a knack for making that type of site.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McDonalds Go&amp;Get</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/mcdonalds-go-and-get</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 12:43:07 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/mcdonalds-go-and-get</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carlsberg Where is the party</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/carlsberg-where-is-the-party</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 12:42:46 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/carlsberg-where-is-the-party</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;tl;dr:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Project for Carlsberg&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Together with North Kingdom&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;An interactive music video to promote Carlsberg&amp;rsquo;s annual &amp;lsquo;Where&amp;rsquo;s the party?&amp;rsquo;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Follow the beat to find out when and where that party is&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Carlsberg annually hosts a rather large party. Summer 2013 they drafted Axwell to perform and wanted to create some hype both for the party and Axwell&amp;rsquo;s new single Center of the universe.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    North Kingdom once again got their creative geniouses going and proposed an interactive video in which the user could find clues to the wherabouts of the party by following the beat. Carlsberg also wanted to hand out merch, making following the beat a sort of competition as well.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Initially, we were just doing backend for the competition, but as time ran short for the NK developers, we also got to do the frontend parts of the competition. We&amp;rsquo;ve never had so many flow charts on the walls of the office! How hard can it be to hand out merch?? With somewhere between 10-20 countries, each with different merch and different rules it caused some severe headaches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What have we done?(!)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The merch was to be distributed randomly; certain times were picked and whoever completed the beat closest after such a time had passed won a piece of merchandise. It was an external party that created the huge file with all the timestamps, we just did the import. Which was difficult enough to get correct, since we had some miscommunications about the ID:s of the different types of merch. Then proceeded checks to verify that there was a timestamp available, that the user had indeed followed the beat correctly and so on. All done in python.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    On the frontend side of things, there were different flows depending on what country you had selected as yours, but other than that it was pretty straight forward HTML and CSS.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Afterwards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    There was a party. Axwell was there. The site won a lot of awards. However, we ourselves look back on this project as one of the tougher ones of 2013; it taught us how important it is to structure code and work load with clear guide lines as to how to do something and who&amp;rsquo;s supposed to do it. We&amp;rsquo;re happy to say we&amp;rsquo;ve improved immensely in these regards.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/samsung-youneedtoseethis</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 12:06:09 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/samsung-youneedtoseethis</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;tl;dr:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Project for Samsung&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Together with Wenderfalck&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;A gigapixel photograph provides the setting to showcase the new screen of Samsung&amp;rsquo;s Tab S&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Zoom, pan and interact with the gigalpixel photograph and find all the details to compete for a spot on the high score&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Early summer 2014 we got a call from our relatively new partner Wenderfalck asking us if we wanted to collaborate on a project for Samsung. We said yes (of course) and together we created this technically challenging application to promote the new tablet Tab S.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What have we done?(!)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The application is a game where the player is presented with a gigapixel photograph in which they can pan and zoom in a &amp;ldquo;google mapsy&amp;rdquo; kind of way. The player is then presented with a hundred items (one at a time) located somewhere in the picture, and the goal is to find them all in the shortest time possible. If an item is particularly hard and the user doesn&amp;rsquo;t find it within 90 seconds, the user has an option to display a hint as to what area the item is in. At any time the user can enter their name to the high score, and their result is updated as they find more items.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    We did the whole technical solution using python, HTML, scss and of course a whole lot of javascript. We chose the angular framework and also took advantage of inuit.css. We had to rack our brains for all our combined image managing knowledge; each photograph in the application had a file size of several gigs; the largest around 15, making them impossible to save in any normal file format. We needed to tile the pictures at several different zoom levels for use in the application, so we manually had to divide them into pieces small enough to save as JPGs, and then run scripts on those files to divide them into tiles of 512x512px. It took a lot of time running those scripts!
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Afterwards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Client happy; we&amp;rsquo;re happy. We&amp;rsquo;re actually rather impressed with ourselves for creating something that works so well in just a few short weeks. So impressed and content with the result that we&amp;rsquo;ve put our image solution (tiling, zooming, panning, etc) up on our GitHub for all you guys out there who don&amp;rsquo;t want to do this from scratch. We hope it&amp;rsquo;ll be of some use!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build with Chrome</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/build-with-chrome</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2014 16:15:51 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/build-with-chrome</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2&gt;tl;dr:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Project for Google and LEGO&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Together with North Kingdom&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Build whatever you want with LEGO, wherever you want in the world&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;A webGL interactive experience to showcase the features of Google Chrome and promote the feature film LEGO the Movie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    By now, Build with Chrome is one our longest running projects. It started in early 2012 when LEGO celebrated 50 years in the land down under, and our partners in crime over at North Kingdom tasked us with making Australia into LEGO-bricks. Said and done, in June that same year, (mainly) Aussies started littering their continent with fantastic LEGO creations and it was a pretty sweet feeling watching the intricate buildings and crazy creatures.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    A year later it was go again; BWC was going global, the experience was getting a few new features and the designs were updated. Once again we worked closely with North Kingdom who came up with a concept of a game mode, where the goal was to become a Master Builder. BWC v2 was released as promotion both for the webGL capacities in Google Chrome as well as the new LEGO the Movie feature film.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What have we done?(!)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    The application is loosely divided into four different sections: Build mode, Explore mode, Academy mode and CMS for the LEGO people to keep an eye on all the creations.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Explore mode&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Entering the Explore mode the user is shown a view of their current geographic location, populated with markers to indicate where people have built their LEGO-structures. Using a zoom control, the user can zoom in on any geographic spot to view the creations in webGL 3D. We used Google Maps&amp;rsquo; API to present the world, where each tile of from the API equaled one baseplate - the unit each user is given upon entering Build mode. Users can either specifically select a base plate in 3D mode, or get one randomly assigned based on their geographical location. We did HTML-templates, javascript, CSS and API integrations.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    The application uses Google+ authentication so users who sign in can view builds created by people in their circles and revisit builds they&#39;ve liked using the +1 feature.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Build mode&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    In Build mode the user is presented with their chosen baseplate on which they are free to create whatever they want with a bunch of LEGO-bricks in different shapes and colours. We were responsible for the UI; rotating bricks, changing colour and brick types, saving and publishing. We worked closely with programmers at NK who did the actual webGL code, while we created HTML-templates, CSS and AJAX API calls to save people&amp;rsquo;s builds.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Academy mode&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Academy consists of a series of challenges of increasing difficulty. The user is to follow a set of instructions (much as in a building with regular LEGO), learning a number of different building techniques, eventually gaining the title of Master builder.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;CMS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    LEGO needed to be able to remove inappropriate content, which is why we created a flagging system accessible from Explore mode. In the CMS the moderators can review all builds created, and work through the ones that have been flagged by users of the application. There is also some statistics and a whole section to translate the whole application to an unlimited number of languages (currently the application is available in 27 languages).
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Afterwards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project cannot be called anything other than a success; at the time of writing there are 678 394 different builds in the Build with Chrome world and the site has had literally millions of visitors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We learned lots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the grande finale of the project we all went to the cinemas and saw LEGO the Movie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ericsson City Index</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/ericsson-city-index</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2014 16:15:51 CEST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/ericsson-city-index</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;tl;dr:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Project for Ericsson&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Together with DDB&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;A business to business/government tool to explain and show off Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s City Index&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Graphs and maps show you how IT-infrastructure affect other aspects of society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Ericsson was looking to renew their City Index tool. They&amp;rsquo;ve gathered loads of metrics from about 30 cities around the world and these numbers show how IT-infrastructure relates to other aspects of society such as literacy rate, health and environmental pollution.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Their old site was built on flash, complete with funny noises and animations on hover. The old site was also only marginally interactive, basically just displaying the different scores. Needless to say, it needed some pimpin&amp;rsquo;. DDB was tasked with said assignment and they wanted to work with us. Being mainly business to business (or at least business to governments) it wasn&amp;rsquo;t the most exciting project we&amp;rsquo;ve ever taken on, but it presented some challenges and we got to try out some new frameworks for real.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What have we done?(!)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    DDB had a lot of features planned for the new site. It started off with a Google Maps populated with a marker for each city that was part of the index. Each city have their own page, where the user can study the different values that city has scored. There are also case studies related to the city.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    It was the express wish that there would be an easy to comprehend comparison view. In the end, we did two: One grid view, where two measurements are displayed on the X- and Y-axies respectively and the cities are marked by dots in the grid. And one with columns in which the values for each measurement could be altered to see how the ranking was affected in real time.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    We couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a suitable lib to help us with the grid view, so in the end we did it from scratch. Ember.js helped us with updating the city models in the column view, but in hindsight it was a bit too much hassle using that particular framework, despite the kind of cute hamster.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Afterwards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The tool was presented internally at Ericsson at an event in Dallas and everyone was pretty pleased. Today we&amp;rsquo;ve just gotten charged with the rest of the Ericsson website, as DDB was that happy working with us.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>William says Hello</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2014-05-08-william-says-hello</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2014-05-08-william-says-hello</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a guest blog post by our 14year old trainee William! Unfortunately available in Swedish only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The following entry is in swedish only.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Den senaste tiden har vi haft förstärkning av William, i normala fall åttondeklassare på Internationella Engelska Skolan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;Jag valde att ha min prao här på grund av att jag har ett stort intresse bland datorer och programmering och det såg roligt ut och det var det.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jag har fått göra en hemsida som var ganska svårt på grund av att det var min första men så tur så fick jag hjälp när jag behövde det och jag har lärt mig mycket av det, innan så visste jag bara &amp;#8216;the basics&amp;#8217; av html och css och nu känns det som jag kan otroligt mycket mer.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;William fick som uppgift av oss att skapa en rolig intern sajt kallad &amp;#8220;Veckans&amp;#8221;.
Konceptet var att under veckans gång kunna lägga in roliga händelser på kontoret och utanför, för att sedan kunna rösta på dessa händelser för att få fram &amp;#8220;veckans händelse&amp;#8221;, t.ex om någon gjort ett roligt misstag i kod, ramlat och slagit sig (slapstick-humor blir aldrig gammalt) eller om någon kanske sagt en rolig wordpun som fick oss alla att skratta.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vår designer Max satt tillsammans med William och skissade fram en enkel wireframe till hur sajten skulle se ut och nästan direkt kunde arbetet med frontend-utveckling påbörjas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full wp-image-374&#34; alt=&#34;william_3&#34; src=&#34;http://blog.agigen.se/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/william_3.jpg&#34; width=&#34;800&#34; height=&#34;600&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Designen i sig var relativt enkel, men även simplistiska layouts kräver mycket CSS &amp;#8211; speciellt eftersom den skulle fungera i både mobil, dator och till och med en TV för våra morgonmöten.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full wp-image-373&#34; alt=&#34;william_2&#34; src=&#34;http://blog.agigen.se/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/william_2.jpg&#34; width=&#34;800&#34; height=&#34;600&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Efter några dagar var grunden klar och det gick att klicka sig runt både i mobil och dator, mission accomplished. Vi kände att det fanns nog med frontend färdigt för att fortsätta med backend-biten själva. Vi tackar William för tiden han kunde ge och önskar honom ett stort lycka till i världen av kod och design!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vi ger William sista ordet:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;Allt var intressant här &amp;#8211; jag fick lära mig mycket och jag gillar allt som jag har gjort. Det var mer än vad jag förväntade mig. Jag trodde jag inte skulle få ha något att göra hela tiden men det fick jag, jag fick göra en hemsida som var otroligt kul.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>